marketsworld.com 2013-01-17

# Privacy Policy | Licensed Binary Options Trading | Markets World

##  Markets World Website Privacy Policy 

Markets World takes the utmost measures to protect your privacy. This privacy policy sets out the data processing practices we carry out through the use of the Internet and any other electronic communications networks. 

### Use of personal information

We collect personal information from visitors to this web site through the use of online forms, transactions you undertake, and information about your visits to our website. We process personal information collected via this website for the purposes of:

  * Providing and personalising our services;

  * Dealing with your enquiries and requests;

  * Carrying out internal marketing research and website development; and

  * Providing you with information about our products, promotions and services.

We will use your email address to send you details of Markets World events, promotions, products and services. You can choose not to receive those emails by following the instructions on the sign up page or via the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of each email. Switching off emails will mean that you miss exclusive promotional offers and information from us. 

We use cookies to identify you when you visit this website. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser to recognize repeat visitors. Our use of cookies allows registered users to be presented with a personalised version of the site and carry out transactions. Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser. Switching off cookies will mean that you will have to log in again each time you use the site. To find out more about the use of cookies visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) . 

We will never sell or disclose any of your personal information or provide it to others for profit. We only disclose your personal information to our own business, suppliers we engage and where required to do so, government bodies and law enforcement agencies. We will check your age, address and credit/debit card details with fraud prevention companies which may store your information on file. We use high-grade 128 bit RC4 encryption through DigiCert to secure the connection between your browser and our website to prevent electronic eavesdropping.

Our web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing this web site and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.

You have the right to access the personal data held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you, or if you have any questions or concerns about anything in this privacy policy, please write to us at [service@marketsworld.com](mailto:%73%65%72%76%69%63%65@%6d%61%72%6b%65%74%73%77%6f%72%6c%64.%63%6f%6d?subject=Privacy%3A%20request%20copy%20of%20my%20personal%20information%20or%20queries%20re%20privacy%20policy) .
